RENATO MAZZILLI

Mail: renmazzilli@gmail.com Phone: +57 3013436120 Portfolio: rokziell.github.io

SUMMARY

I'm a game developer with 4 years of experience and a master in game design and development from UNIR University. I have +2 years of experience as project manager in game development verifying the assets are in line with the Game Design Document of the project. I'm fluent in English and Spanish to stablish a great communication between teams.

TOOLS

Game Engines

- Unity 3D.
- Unreal Engine.
- Phaser.

Programming Languages

- C#.
- JavaScript.
- Visual Scripting

Version Control

GitHub.

Team Management

- ClickUp.
- Jira.
- Asana.
- Slack.

SKILLS

- Positive attitude, and the ability to work in highly collaborative team environment
- Ability to learn new tools in a quickly and efficient way.
- Ability to create immersive levels.
- Ability to create immersive systems and game mechanics.

EXPERIENCE

DOUBLE FOX GAMES

August 2021 – Present: Programmer.

Responsibilities as Game Developer:

- Develop effective prototypes of hyper casuals games of high quality.
- Estimate development time in order to assure a delivery on time of the product.
- Design and development of main systems to create an amazing user experience.
- Collaborate with art and 3d departments in order to assure an excellent implementation following the artistic vision of the game.

ABO KASHEM MOBILE (PROJECT)

July 2020 - December 2020: Level Designer.

Responsibilities as Level Designer:

- Use the exclusive Abo Kashem Engine to create unique, fun and interesting environments of the game focused on combat, platforming and exploration.
- Dressing the level.
- Manage my time to deliver the level on the according to deadlines.

SANDSTORM STUDIOS

February 2019 - June 2020: Level Designer, Project Manager & Game Designer

Responsibilities as Level Designer:

- Create unique, fun and interesting environments for kids in gamification projects.
- Create the layout of the level.
- Create the hub world of games.
- Create level design that supports and encourage exploration on the level.

Responsibilities as Project Manager:

- Lead a team of 4 people to finished projects.
- Set a scrum for different projects.
- Commit to weekly deadlines.

Responsibilities as Game Designer:

- Developed different games ideas for gameplay on gamification projects.
- Create new and fun game experiences to learn specific objectives of a subject through a videogame.
- Developed game's simple story for gamification projects.

BILINGUAL AGENT ON CUSTOMER SERVICE

June 2018 – September 2018: Bilingual Agent.

Responsibilities as an Agent:

- Receive international calls to give medical information.
- Receive international calls to advise the client about their medical policy.
- Make follow up calls from users that request that call.
- Write documentation about the user interaction during the call.

EDUCATION

UNIR – MSc. Game Design and Development	(2020 - 2021)
Coursera - Introduction to Game Development	2020
Coursera - Principles of Game Design	2020
Coursera - Business of Games and Entrepreneurship	2020
Coursera - Game Development for Modern Platforms	2020
Coursera - Pixel Art for Videogames	2020
Coursera - Low Poly Art For Video Games	2020
Universidad del Atlántico - Architecture	(Graduated 2018)
Unity Certified Developer	2018